CV Benjamin Van Renterghem

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name: Benjamin Van Renterghem

Birth Date: 05-01-1997

Address: Brugsestraat 111/3, 8020 Oostkamp, Belgium

Mobile: +32 471 28 25 74

E-mail: benjamin@bvrcode.com

Social: <u>linkedin.com</u>/in/benjamin-vr

github.com/BenjaVR

stackoverflow.com/users/6077371/benjavr

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a freelance software developer with some years of experience in the full stack .NET ecosystem. I have a strong focus on front-end web development, and want to further pursue this road.

My goal is to help companies build nice and intuitive user interfaces, setup/maintain/improve the code infrastructure, while also coaching in the process. UI and UX are subjects that interest me a lot, which helps me be a better front-end developer and reach that goal.

I always look for opportunities to learn new things and I am aware of the latest and most modern technologies. Sharing that knowledge is something I find extremely important, and it is something I really enjoy.

Apart from web development, I have a personal interest in mobile development, as well as in machine learning and AI related topics.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 - 2018: Internship

Infohos Services

Machine Learning in healthcare sector (research)

2018 - present: Full Stack .NET Web Developer

Infohos Solutions / ZORGI

Working on Electronic Health Record (Medicatiebeheer, EPD) and in-house React

component library

2020 - present: Freelance Software Developer

BVR Code (self-employment) @ Upwork (upwork.com)

Small freelance jobs on weekends, such as:

- Automating webshop infrastructure using Node.js @ tezzex.com
- Mobile application using React Native @ matchupapp.net

- ...

2020 - present: Front-end/full-stack Developer

BVR Code (self-employment) @ Bingli (mybingli.com)

Building an internal analysis tool using Python and Angular with focus on the

front-end.

SIDE PROJECTS

U2be website: Website for a Belgian U2 tribute band, based on the original U2 website

https://u2be.eu

Made with PHP and October CMS

Student Planner: Web app for a organization to manage student internships from different schools

https://stud-plan.web.app (login required)

Made with TypeScript, React and Firebase (Cloud Functions and Firestore)

EDUCATION

2017 - 2017: Ingeniero en Sistemas Computacionales

Tecnológico de Monterrey (QRO) International semester in Mexico

2015 - 2018: Bachelor Applied Computer Science

Howest Bruges

Software and System Engineering

2013 - 2015: Human Science – Mathematics

Sint-Franciscus-Xaveriusinstituut Bruges

Highschool

2011 - 2013: Economics – Mathematics

Sint-Franciscus-Xaveriusinstituut Bruges

Highschool

2009 - 2011: Latin

Spes Nostra Zedelgem

Highschool

SKILLS

I am proficient at ...

- TypeScript / JavaScript
- React
- Node.js
- HTML / CSS / Sass
- Webpack / NPM
- C#
- .NET (Core) / ASP.NET

I know how to work with ...

- iQuery
- Knockout

- Angular
- React Native
- Node.js
- Firebase / Firestore (nosql)
- MSSQL / MySQL (relational databases)
- Git / Subversion
- VB.NET
- Adobe XD

I have used ...

- WPF / UWP
- Electron
- Vue
- PHP / Laravel / OctoberCMS
- MongoDB
- Python / Django / Flask
- Jupyter / Scikit-learn / Pandas / ML.NET
- Kotlin / Java / Android

LANGUAGES

- Dutch (primary language)
- English (fluent)
- French (very basic)

OTHER ACTIVITIES

2017 - present: Drums / music

2013 - 2019: Kitchen help in De Lekpot Loppem (weekends and holidays / flexijob)

2005 - 2016: Basketball in competition